The Stare and Run Championship.
You heard "goo."
I'm not watching it this time.
"The Stare and Run Championship."
This time, I'm going for white.
If we win...
I'll have Sakurazu's skin, but I'll be fine.
Then go for it.
That's not true.
What?
Sakurazu?
Why not?
You'll decide, won't you?
If we win, I'll take that as well.
It's not like we're going to win.
I'm going to wear this dark symbol.
I'm gonna wear the gray hat.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm not a housewife.
Not a housewife.
It doesn't fit.
What did you think?
You're so far ahead of me.
Did she go in the fall?
It's not right.
If we win...
When I was MC.
I asked you where you were in high school art class.
Yeah.
He took it very seriously.
I heard you went to bed early.
Yeah, I did everything and went to bed.
First of all, I'd like you to draw my portrait.
Do we have a time limit?
Twenty seconds.
20 seconds. That's short.
Now that's short.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
I'd like to go now to the survey.
Are you ready?
I'll do my best.
Okay, here we go.
All right, let's go!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Here we go!
Oh, man, this is pretty good.
I really couldn't tell where the eyes, mouth and nose were.
But if you keep staring at me...
20 seconds is hard.
If I could draw it, I could draw it!
This is the flower from Ayara's point of view, right?
Yes, yes, yes...
That's right.
This is how the flower looks from Ayara's point of view.
I drew it from my heart.
I'm so happy.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's good, isn't it?
Blah, blah, blah.
Crackle.
Okay, we're ready to go.
Yes, sir.
It's going to be "Ichikawa-san's Challenge".
Leave it to me.
Itch.
I knew it. We're partners.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
We've been playing together for a long time.
I've been beside you for 10 years. I've been watching you from the side.
Right.
All right, start!
That's a scary sound.
Doesn't it make you nervous?
Aren't you nervous to draw while looking at it?
Ten seconds.
Three, two, one.
That's it.
This is not good.
Oh, my God.
I wrote it on my face.
I'm like an old man from a Disney cartoon or something.
Grandpa.
But that's okay, he's a Disney character.
Disney characters!
It's cute!
It's like that.
I might want to work out a little bit.
I'm looking forward to it.
Next, we have Mr. Suzuki's challenge.
Yes, Hana always makes fun of me.
He asked me to draw the same picture.
He drew a lot of pictures, so I drew a lot of pictures, and then he laughed at me.
He looked at it and said, "I'll show you.
So today, I'd like to make up for that.
I'd like to find something that I'm better than you.
I'll do my best.
You're right.
Now, let's see what Mr. Suzuki can do.
Here we go.
Are you okay?
20 seconds?
Ten seconds left.
I'm looking at him intently.
Three twenty-one.
We're done.
Which way would you draw your eyebrows if you drew them the first time?
Which way would you draw it if you drew it the first time?
Which way would you draw it if you drew it for the first time?
Oh, no.
Why did you draw your eyebrows twice?
Because I'm kind of a screamer.
Wait a minute.
Let's draw them in order.
When you've drawn them in order, here they are.
There you go!
Don't touch my chin.
Do I look like this?
This one... sticks out.
A black eye.
The black eye is not in the eyeball.
It's like this.
Thank you.
It's still like this.
It's okay.
Okay, then.
Chin.
We're in this together.
Hey, you!
What?
I thought we're the same.
No, we're not.
No, it's not.
Why is it like that?
If I had a chin, it would be longer.
It's been bothering me lately.
You're in the same position.
You're saying I have a long chin.
You're saying I have a long chin?
I've been getting that a lot lately.
A little bit.
It's been bothering me lately.
I've been getting comments in the comments section about my long chin.
Next.
Shupi.
I've got a lot of doodles.
Oops.
My skin.
What do you think?
While taking care of it
Well, I'll be careful in a couple of weeks.
That's right.
It's a good thing I'm cynical.
And it's great.
That's great.
I feel like I've been feeling really down in the dumps.
Okay, then.
Here's my hand.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Wow.
It's so bad that you care.
It's so bad.
You shortened my face.
That's right.
Scary monster.
Stop being a monster!
Stop being a monster.
One or the other.
Let's see.
First, I drew the first eyebrow here.
And then the second and final one here.
I'm drawing an eyebrow here.
By the way, what's this hand doing?
Oh, my God, what is that?
I don't know.
Bangs?
Bangs.
Yeah, we've all seen them.
Yes, we all see them.
Okay, this time...
I'll be in Shimonoseki.
What's this?
Laughs.
Honestly...
Decide.
Go on, go on, go on!
Hey, impart.
LOL.
So, can I ask you to look at them side by side for a second?
Boo hoo here.
It makes me happy.
In my dreams...
I'm going to write a group. I've already decided to do it.
My chin is high. It's on my chin.
I've decided to write a group of moles on my face.
He's got a lot of moles on his face. It's an assertive one.
He cared about me.
He cared about me?
Is that caring?
Stare at it for the second time.
Why are you so glamorous?
Blow off! I'm too soppy!
I'm too bloated.